There was an interest savings account
that I was very interested in in an
earlier
stage of life, almost by accident.
And at 24,
instead of trying to buy a house,
or instead of trying to get crypto, or
instead of trying to do any of these
things,
I decided my interest savings account
was going to be an audience.
And I knew that I could pay into
that interest
savings account every time I created a
piece of content.
So every time I made a reel,
every time I made a tweet,
every time I wrote an
email, I was in essence,
not just paying into my interest savings
account,
but I was being able to impact it on a
daily or even hourly
basis.
Whereas if you put something in the S&P
500, you've got to sit
back and wait for ages.
When you look to build an audience,
you are in control of
that investment fully, wholly.
You have a video
that outperforms all the other
videos, your share prices go up
and it can impact your business.
I can see on a day-by-day basis,
the financial position of my
business is impacted by paying in,
just like I am now with this
video. And for a lot of young people,
and again,
not everyone has what it takes to
build an audience, post for years,
create a business, serve people online,
whatever
it is. But for a lot of people, you do.
Now, similarly to a lot of investments,
if you put money in in the first year,
you're not going to see a massive amount
back. But in social media, 100% you could.
And there are people, even in my program,
that are thinking about going to uni and
doing a master's, and I'm like, "Cool,
you can spend a year or several years
becoming better educated, and
if you're a doctor or surgeon
or you're flying a
plane, cool." But if you
were to spend those four years instead
making better content,
producing YouTube videos,
learning how to use Photoshop for
thumbnails,
you can drastically impact the level
and quality of your life and the
people around you.
And no one's really had
that opportunity before